frenchentree.com 2004-12-08

# Privacy Policy & Terms & Conditions: FrenchEntrée.com

| Site Contents  
---  
Home  
Welcome  
Search  
Discussion Forum  
The Directory  
Free Newsletter  
Limousin Site  
Book Reviews  
Weather & Climate  
Currency Converter  
Metric Converter  
Property Zone  
Properties for sale  
French antiques  
Food & shopping  
Finance Zone  
Currency Zone  
Legal & Tax Zone  
Health Zone  
Education Zone  
Regions Zone  
Transport & Travel Zone  
Removals Zone  
La Vie Zone  
We Made It Zone  
Advertise  
Feedback  
Links to & from us  
Link Directory  
About Us  
Terms & Conditions  
Private LogIn  
|   

**YOUR PRIVACY**

**Information Collection and Use**  
We collect information from our users during the Registration process - this is for administration and contact purposes in connection with contributions you may wish to make to the site or your use of certain site features such as newsletter subscriptions or discussion forums. FrenchEntrée.com is the sole owner of the personal information collected from this site. Your data is held secure by us and will not be transmitted , rented or sold to any third party. We reserve the right to contact you via the email address you provide with information about the site or about related products and services.  
**Order Forms**  
From time to time we may sell products on our site and in this instance we will request information from users on our order forms. Users have to provide contact information (such as name and delivery address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiry date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill customer orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.  
**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file written to a user’s hard drive that contains the User ID. The cookies do not contain any personal information about users. The use of cookies is now widespread. The reason we use cookies is so that we can personalise a user's experience of the site. If a user sets up his browser to reject the cookie, he or she may still use the site although some functionality will be impaired. If you don't wish to have cookies stored on your computer, you can find instructions on how to block them HERE [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html "http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html") . For more information on cookies including UK legislation, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ "http://www.allaboutcookies.org")  
**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.  
**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FrenchEntrée.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of these third party sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
**Removing Personal Information**  
Users may contact us at any time to change or remove personal data. Contact [service@frenchentree.com](mailto:service@frenchentree.com "mailto:service@frenchentree.com")   
**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes in this article, linked from our Homepage, so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**TERMS & CONDITIONS OF USE**

If you use the FrenchEntrée.com website (the "Website") you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions.

**1.Definitions**  
In these terms and conditions, "we" and "us" means FrenchEntrée.com, which is a trading name of Content Development Limited (company number 2814734), whose registered office is The Old House, Main Street, Maids Moreton, BUCKINGHAM, MK18 1QU, United Kingdom.   
**2.Access to the Website and content**  
2.1 The information provided by us on the Website is not in any way an invitation or recommendation to buy any products or services featured and you should seek appropriate independent advice.   
2.2 We will endeavour to allow uninterrupted access to the Website, but access to the Website may be suspended, restricted or terminated at any time.   
2.3 We reserve the right to change, modify, substitute or remove without notice any information on the Website from time to time.   
2.4 We assume no responsibility for the contents of any other websites to which the Website has links.   
**3\. Intellectual Property**  
3.1 Unless specifically stated otherwise the copyright in the material contained in the Website belongs to Content Development Limited, its subsidiaries or the providers of such information. All rights are reserved. None of this material may be reproduced or redistributed without our written permission. You may, however, download or print a single copy for your own non-commercial viewing.   
3.2 FrenchEntrée.com is a trademark of Content Development Limited. Other product and company names mentioned on this website may be the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.   
3.3 You shall retain ownership of all copyright in data you submit to the Website. Unless otherwise specifically agreed between us in writing you grant us a world-wide exclusive, royalty-free, non-terminable licence to use, copy, distribute, publish and transmit such data in any manner.   
**4.Exclusions of liability**  
4.1 We use reasonable endeavours to ensure that the data on the Website is accurate and to correct any errors or omissions as soon as practicable after being notified of them. We do not monitor, verify or endorse information submitted by third parties for posting on the Website and you should be aware that such information may be inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. To the extent permitted by applicable law, we disclaim all warranties and representations (whether express or implied) as to the accuracy of any information contained on the Website. We do not guarantee that the Website will be fault free and do not accept liability for any errors or omissions.   
4.2 Due to the nature of electronic transmission of data over the internet, and the number of users by whom data is posted on to the Website, any liability we may have for any losses or claims arising from an inability to access the Website, or from any use of the Website or reliance on the data transmitted using the Website, is excluded to the fullest extent permissible by law. In no event shall we be liable for any loss of profit, revenues, goodwill, opportunity, business, anticipated savings or other indirect or consequential loss of any kind in contract, tort (including negligence) or otherwise arising out of use of the Website, save where such liability cannot be excluded by law.   
4.3 We do not give any warranty that the Website is free from viruses or anything else which may have a harmful effect on any technology.  
**5.Exclusion of liability for suppliers' goods and services**  
We promote a number of suppliers on the Website and offer you the opportunity to buy goods and services from those suppliers through the Website. We can accept no liability for any goods or services provided by third party suppliers. Any goods or services which are not stated to be provided by us are provided by third parties over whom we do not have control and you should satisfy yourself that you wish to purchase those goods or services before contracting with the supplier. The suppliers will be supplying on their own standard terms and conditions and you should check that you agree to those terms and conditions before placing an order.   
**6\. User name and password**  
6.1 On registering with us, you are issued with a user name and password which must be used in order to access certain restricted parts of the Website. The user name and password are personal to you and are not transferable.   
6.2 Your name and password are the methods used by us to identify you and so are very important. You are responsible for all information posted on the Website by anyone using your user name and password and any payments due for services accessed through the Website by anyone using your user name and password. Any breach of security of a user name and password should be notified to us immediately.   
6.3 You may not adapt or circumvent the systems in place in connection with the Website nor access the Website other than through normal operations.   
**7\. Data submitted by users**  
7.1 We accept no liability for data supplied by any user for display on the Website and the limitations in condition 4 above (Exclusions of liability) apply.   
7.2 If you submit data for display on the Website you are responsible for ensuring that the data is accurate, complete and up to date and for updating that data where necessary. Posting of your contribution to the Website does not in any way indicate our approval or endorsement of the content. We reserve the right to determine whether or not to post your contribution to the Website, where on the site it will appear and for how long.   
7.3 If you submit data for display on the Website you are responsible for ensuring that no data is uploaded or submitted which is untrue, defamatory, obscene or abusive or otherwise objectionable or in breach of any applicable laws or rights of third parties.   
7.4 You warrant that you have taken all reasonable precautions to ensure that any data you upload or otherwise submit to the Website is free from viruses and anything else which may have a contaminating or destructive effect on any part of the Website or any other technology.   
7.5 We reserve the right (without limiting our rights to seek other remedies) to remove offending material placed on the Website that we consider to constitute a misuse of the Website or which is otherwise harmful to other users of the Website.   
7.6 You will indemnify us for any claim or loss (including without limitation, economic loss) suffered by us arising out of your failure to observe any of the terms of this condition 7.   
7.7 Subject to the Contracts (Rights of Third Parties) Act 1999 condition 7.5 may be enforced by the following people in their own right:   
a.) any third party with whom we contract for content or advertising; and  
b.) our employees or agents   
at the time of any failure to observe.  
**8\. Data protection**  
8.1 We are committed to protecting your privacy. We will collect and use information supplied by you and other users of the Website to improve the Website and personalise your experience when you visit the Website. We may also use it to tell you about changes in our services or about features we think you'll find interesting including related products from third-parties who provide complementary services. By registering with us, you are deemed to have consented to use of personal information for these purposes. However, you can tell us not to deal with your personal information in these ways in the future by simply sending an e-mail message to [service@frenchentree.com](mailto:service@frenchentree.com "mailto:service@frenchentree.com")   
8.2 Under the UK Data Protection Act 1998 we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access.   
**9\. Termination**  
9.1 We may terminate your access to the Website and the services within it on not less than three days' written notice to you.   
9.2 All disclaimers, indemnities and exclusions in this agreement shall survive termination of this Agreement for any reason.   
**10 General**  
10.1 If any provision of these terms and conditions is held to be unlawful, invalid or unenforceable, that provision shall be deemed severed and the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions of these terms and conditions shall not be affected.   
10.2 We may modify these terms and conditions at any time by publishing the modified terms and conditions on the Website. Any modifications shall take effect 3 days after posting on the Website.   
**11\. Governing law**  
11.1 These terms are governed by and to be construed in accordance with English law.   
11.2 Any disputes shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the English courts. We shall not be liable if the content of this website or any viewing of it by you is contrary to the laws applying in the place where you access this website.

FrenchEntrée Home Page

|  **French Property Tips** your **FREE** newsletter.   
Type in your email to subscribe: Your email address is not provided to anyone else - see Privacy Policy for full details.   
View Previous Newsletters

[

](http://bpc.barclays.fr/ebn.ebn?pid=192&domain=site&rub=25&object=rubrique&id=25 "http://bpc.barclays.fr/ebn.ebn?pid=192&domain=site&rub=25&object=rubrique&id=25")

 **Looking for property or planning a move to Limousin?** Check out the new FrenchEntrée Limousin site...
